businessknowhow.com 2018-10-02

# Business Know-How® Privacy Statement

Business Know-How, a dba of Attard Communications, Inc. is an award-winning small business website for home offices and small businesses. The website provides practical information, how-to articles, tools and resources for starting, growing and managing small and home-based businesses.

Business Know-How is committed to maintaining your trust. Our privacy policy will assist you in understanding how we use the personal information you provide to us.

**Privacy of our email lists**  
Attard Communications, Inc maintains several email lists to keep our web site members informed about new features and events. Our list is made up only of those individuals who specifically request and confirm that they want their name be added to our mailing list. A subscriber can opt-out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of emails that BusinessKnowHow sends.

We do not sell,rent, loan, trade, or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. From time to time, we do send out special offers on behalf of advertisers to our members. When we do such mailings, the advertisers send us the advertisements, and we send the email. Thus  the advertisers do not have access to your personal contact information unless you respond to their ads and provide them with personal information yourself.

**Personal Information**

When you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form, we collect your email address and other data you enter into the forms. We use that information to deliver our newsletter or any giveaways you may have requested.  If you take one of our surveys, we may aggregate the responses you provide with those of other respondents to produce and publish reports that describe the overall results of the survey. Such reports indicate information such as the percentage of users who responded in a certain way to questions.    

**Browser information collected on the website**  
Attard Communications, Inc. analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. 

**Use of cookies** **  
**BusinessKnowHow.com uses cookies. We use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services.

Business Know-How uses Google Analytics to track how visitors interact with and move through our website.

Google is a third-party vendor that uses cookies for ad personalization and measurement to serve ads on Business Know-How website.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Opting out:** **  
**Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the[Google Ad Settings](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on. 

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, lead forms, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

      • On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

      • By emailing us

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.  

For further information, please contact Janet Attard, Attard Communications, Inc., 80 Orville Dr. Suite 100, Bohemia, NY 11716 (631)-467-8883. email: [[email protected]](https://www.businessknowhow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#34554040554650745641475d5a5147475f5a5b435c5b431a575b59)
